So they have seen that hard drives do not
really benefit from memory which they don't get much
faster and also which d capacities
improving this speed it is very very slow
so one question with d rams especially d
rams and benefiting from more d in terms
of capacity so d cotton it is
growing about this fast is d capacity
of hard drive but whether they are faster than
hard drive hard drive system are about let take
10 minutes in ikons
ram ax terms and well inside a
microsikon so they are talking about it
list three orders of magnet is speed
difference so d region they normally do not use
memories per storage is dat d hard
drive are about d 100 times cheaper per
gigabyte however d ram are times c in d
hard drive so people come up with this a de
of solid state this is the which really is not a this cat
which it just solid
state means electronic storage but
because  It is intended this reply
and a controller data would refresh seat and they have a
battery so data they can
run conference and not close it this is very fast it is actually very little more
reliable than a hard drive but it is
extremely expensive and it is not good for
collecting data because
you run out of data and they lose data for a really
long time today today there is an
option which is flash memory so flash is
fabricated in similar technology to the
one data is used for making RAMs and
processors and it is its transistor
big ben office promos it has weak
variable power because unlike at dispense
which time and when you are not using it
flash will it consumes very very little
power and also it does not need to move
other heads or anything it is very fast very fast and this is the
slogan
and it has  Give smaller capacity This
because I
love without power so you can store something in a
flash Forget about it per seven
years and you probably still be able to
read it what is it every you are bats